You know, you know what happened to me a few
years ago, when, when I was young…?  When I was,
when I was younger, huh?  When I was
younger, because I'm still, I'm still young,
right?  I'm still young.  But when I was
even younger, younger and more handsome,
even more handsome, when I was
even more handsome than I am,
an incredible thing happened to me.  Incredible.  You won't
believe it.  You won't believe it, it's incredible.
Well, it turns out I was living in Madrid
at that time.  I was in Madrid, I
was studying at the university.  I was, I
was very young, man, I was very young.  I was, I
don't know, 19 or 20 years old.  He was, he was practically a
child.  And he was very shy, very shy.  I didn't have, I did
n't have many friends, I was, I was ashamed of
everything.  He didn't go out, he almost never went out.  I
spent my nights alone, and, and, and the
weekends too, alone, in my house, bored.
Well, it turns out that, uh, one night... it was
winter, I remember it was winter.  It was
a Saturday night.  Yeah, it was a Saturday
night, and instead of being out on the street, uh,
having fun with, with, with young people
my age, I was at home.  I was at home,
alone, in my apartment.  A very small apartment,
in the center of Madrid, old, okay?
And, well, it was winter and it was very cold.  It was
an apartment, it was an apartment without heating.  It had no
heating.  So, at about 9 o'clock, I
went to bed, right?  I would get into bed,
grab a book and a glass of warm milk,
okay?  A cup, a cup of hot milk.  And,
and, and there, and there I would stay for two or three
hours, until, until I fell
asleep, until I got sleepy, right?
And I remember that it was windy outside, it
was raining, it was, it was, it was a
terrible night.  It was a dog's night.  But well,
that, that was my life.  That, that was my life, eh,
back then.  What do you want, what do you want me to
tell you?  It is, it is the truth.  Hey?  It's the truth.
Many people ask me: "But Juan,
the stories you tell in your books,
in, in your videos, in the podcast, in,
in the courses, in the... my courses, my courses
of... my online courses to learn Spanish,
are full of stories."  Because I believe that you
learn a language very well with stories,
right?  In this case, Spanish, right?  You learn in
context, you learn almost without realizing it, right?
I use, I use stories a lot.  I love,
I love using stories.  I think it's
a fantastic way to learn vocabulary,
grammar... And many people ask me: "But Juan,
are those stories true? Are they, are they real?"
Absolutely, absolutely.  I don't know how to lie.  I
don't know how to lie.  I don't know how to lie.  And I don't have, I don't have
imagination, man.  I have no imagination.  I don't,
I wouldn't have, I wouldn't have the imagination to
invent all these stories that I
tell you here, in, in my videos and, and in my courses.  Not at
all, not at all.
No, no, no.  It's all true.  It's all true.
Well, it turns out that that night it was already, I do
n't know, 11:30 or even later... there was a
knock at the door.  There was a knock at the door, someone
knocked at the door: knock knock knock knock, with the, with
the, with the knuckles, right?  Tun tun tun tun.  No,
not with the doorbell, because the doorbell, the doorbell,
I think it didn't work, right?  Then there was a knock
on the door: tun tun tun tun.
I, honestly, I, I, I was a little scared,
right?  Because no one ever came to
see me.  The neighbors were all very unfriendly, they
didn't greet me when they saw me on the
stairs.  I really disliked them all.  No,
no, they didn't tell me anything, man, they didn't tell me
anything.  I had been living there for two or three
months, and no one said anything to me, didn't say
hello to me, didn't... anything to me.  And I hated them all.
So of course, I didn't, I didn't know who, who
could, who it could be.  Me, me… I didn’t know,
right?  So I didn't... at first I didn't pay attention,
right?  I thought, "Well, if I don't open it, he'll leave,
right? He'll leave, he'll think, he'll think... whoever it is
will think I'm not home," right?  Clear.
But no, man, this person kept calling:
tun tun tun tun, tun tun tun tun, and getting louder and
louder: tun tun tun tun, tun tun tun tun.
Sure, I was a little scared, man, I was
a little scared.  But in the end, in the end,
I don't know, I got up.  I thought: "Look, let's see if, let's
see if something happened, what do I know."  I got up.
But since I was scared, I thought maybe it was
someone… some thief who came to rob me,
right?  Or to do something bad to me, hurt me,
hit me… I don’t know, I don’t know.  I got very
nervous, I got very nervous.  I grabbed a hammer, there
was a hammer there on a table, because I'd
been hanging a picture, right?  And,
and I took a hammer and, and I, I put it behind me.
I was in my pajamas, man.  I woke up,
I woke up in my pajamas, with my
pajama pants and my pajama jacket,
okay?  I always, always sleep in pajamas,
right? In winter and in summer.  Well, I put,
I put the hammer here behind, hidden in my
pants but behind, right?  So, okay?  There I
put myself, I put the, the, the hammer, man.  And
I went to open the door, I went to open the door.
But before opening, I looked, I looked through the
peephole, right?  Through the peephole.  Doors,
doors have a peephole, a little hole,
right?  A little hole here, on this side,
and also here, right?  To see, to see
the person who, who comes to your house, right?  Sure,
to know who it is, right?  There's a peephole, a peephole
to look through, isn't there?  I looked through the peephole and saw a
girl.  To a girl, a young girl, a little bit
younger than me, okay?  One, a brunette girl,
like that, with hair, with curly hair.  It
was, it was the nanny.  The
upstairs neighbors' babysitter.  I recognized her.  It was the
nanny who worked upstairs,
the family upstairs.  The family that lived upstairs
had a child, a little boy, right?  And they had
hired this nanny.  And she was French.  I, I
knew her because she was the only one, she was the only one who
greeted me on the stairs, right?  When he saw me he
would say, "Hello, good morning," and so on, right?  She was
the only, only person who greeted me in
the whole house: the nanny of, of the neighbors upstairs.
So, well, I said, "Oh, well, okay."  So I
opened the door without any problems, right?  And there she was,
there she was the girl.  And he started saying to me: "Come,
come. Hey, you have to come, you have to come."
The aunt spoke, she spoke regular Spanish,
okay?  He spoke regularly.  Uh, she was French,
and I think she was in Spain studying
Spanish, right?  He was very young, wasn't he?  And I think she
studied Spanish and made a
little money working as a nanny, right?
So, he started telling me: "Come, come,
you have to come," and so on.  "You have to come,
there's a problem, I'm scared."  It started,
it started to… she was a little hysterical,
wasn't she?  I was a little hysterical.  I didn't really understand
what she meant and why she wanted me to, she
wanted me to go with her to the house
upstairs, because there was a problem,
but I didn't really understand what the problem was.
And well, then well, uh... in the end I said to him:
"Well, look, calm down, what's going on? What
's the problem? What, what, what happened?"  And,
and the aunt… well, a little in Spanish, a little in
French —because I studied French at school,
so I understand a little— a little
in Spanish, a little in French… In the end
I understood that what was happening was that this girl,
well, she had been left alone with the child,
okay?  With the little boy, a 3 or
4 year old boy, and the parents had gone out to dinner,
right?  Saturday night, they had, they had gone out to
dinner, and she, well, had stayed with the child.
And then she told me that she had put the child to bed, she
had put him to bed, in his crib,
a small bed, and she, well, she had
stayed a bit like that, uh... in the house.  He had
gone to the bathroom and, when he was peeing,
he says that when he was peeing he felt,
all of a sudden, a, a look.  All this, all this, he
told me half in Spanish, half in French,
right?, like, as you can imagine.
And, and I was very surprised.  I,
I was, uh… well, I mean, I didn't know what to
think, right?  This whole story… suddenly
this aunt tells me this whole story, right?   She
told me she was, uh, sitting on the toilet,
peeing—okay, she told me that—and she said that
when she was there, she felt like a look, right?    She
felt like a look, that someone was watching her.
And I told her… I thought: "This girl is crazy. This
girl is crazy, she's crazy."  How,
how…?  But what does it say, right?  And the, and the aunt:
"Yes, yes, yes, yes, I have noticed, I have noticed that
someone was watching me, watching me," right?
The aunt told me that she started looking like that
around the bathroom, and suddenly,
suddenly she saw two eyes, two eyes like that, big,
enormous, that were staring at her, right?  And,
and it was, and… it was a spider.  He told me it was a
spider.  A huge spider.  A huge,
hairy spider, with lots of hair, right?  Some, some
legs, some very long legs and a
very big mouth, even with teeth, he told me.
I thought... I thought: "She's crazy,
this girl. This girl is crazy.
I don't know, she's crazy."  But how,
how come… how come there is a huge spider?
Well, I thought that... I thought it was... I don't know, I thought that
maybe he was taking the piss.  I thought it was
a joke.  I thought that… well, I thought a lot of things.
But anyway, in the end, in the end... well,
in the end I went with her, didn't I?  Because I saw her, I
saw that she was so nervous.  He said to me, "Yes, come
with me, please, come with me, because the child
is in bed. I want... I want you to... I want you to
kill the spider."  He told me that… he told me, he
told me that, that I had to kill the spider.
And me, well... well, me, how, how am I going to kill
a spider?  Me... I don't kill anyone, I don't kill a
fly, right?  I don't like killing animals,
or insects, or anything, okay?  And… but the aunt insisted, did
n’t she?  In the end I went upstairs with her, did
n't I?  And he took me to the, to the bathroom.  He took me to the
bathroom and said, "There's the bathroom."
But she didn't want to go in, man.  She: "I'm not going
in, I'm not going in there, I'm not going in there. I'm
scared."  And, and well, of course, I, well, I
also, I felt a little like that, like very… eh,
a little brave, right?  I had to play that
role, didn't I?  It was… I, well, I was very shy,
I wasn't used to going out with girls,
right?  So, for me it was also an opportunity
to show that I was a brave man,
right?, that I could defend a woman and all that.
So: "Don't worry, don't worry, I
'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to fix this problem."
Of course, I thought that was going to be very
easy, right?  Uh… what I wanted was [ __ ] a glass,
right?  I wanted, I didn't want to kill the, the spider, I
wanted [ __ ] a glass and a piece of paper, right?  A glass,
and it said… eh, come on, that's what my mother did
at home, right?  I would take a, a glass, right? I would put it on,
boom, on top of, the chandelier, okay?  And then with a piece of
paper underneath, okay?, uh… I would hunt, I would hunt the
spider and then I would put it outside the house, okay?
That way I didn't kill the spider, no, I didn't hurt it, I
simply put it outside the house.  And I wanted to
do the same thing because I'd seen it in my house
many times, right?  I said: "Well, this woman is
crazy, this... I don't know, I don't know what... how... We are, we are
in Spain, man, there are no
such huge spiders here, right? Anyway..."
The woman stayed outside, I closed the bathroom door
so the spider wouldn't get out, and I stayed there,
hm... anyway, eh... looking for this spider on
the walls.  And I didn't, I didn't see anything, right?
Suddenly, suddenly I felt a noise behind
me, right?  Uh… I was looking, and all of a sudden I heard
a noise behind me, something like scrshhh, okay?  And I
turned around.  I turned around and saw the spider.
I saw the spider… well, I saw a leg, a leg of
the spider.  Uh… because I turned around and,
and when I turned around, the spider, which had come out,
hid, right?  He hid behind the mirror.
There was a mirror in the bathroom, he hid behind
the mirror.  But one… the… you could see the leg.
There was… the leg was out, wasn't it?  There was a, a
… a leg sticking out, right?, with a lot of hair.   It
was… true, it was… a lot of hair.  It had like
yellow and black colors, right? Like a tiger, right?  It was
huge, it was huge.  I, at that moment, at
that moment I [ __ ] on top of me.  I [ __ ] on top of him.
Uh... uh... it scared me, it scared me a lot, man, because
the leg was huge.  And, I mean, I realized that
the spider was behind the mirror, right? But it was
so big that, that the, the leg was sticking out.  No,
no, no, I couldn't get it inside.
So, of course, I [ __ ], I said to myself:
"Ah, [ __ ], it's true, it's true that it's
big."  It's exactly like the girl said, isn't it
? Like Marie, the, the French one—I didn't
say it, her name was Marie.  It's the same as
what my aunt told me, right?
So, al… So, well,
uh… I said: "Well, we have to, we have to, we have to
, we have to [ __ ] to, to, to this, of course,
to this, this spider. It can be dangerous."  In the
end, this French aunt was right.
The nanny was right.  It could be poisonous, right?
Then I remembered, I remembered something… something I
had read in a newspaper, right?, that a woman
had found a huge, very big spider
in a box of kiwis.  I had gone to the supermarket, I had
bought kiwis, right?, a box, and, and,
and there was… and inside the box there was a spider
typical of Australia or, of New Zealand, I don't know.
And I [ __ ], I [ __ ], I [ __ ] on top of it.  I say:
"[ __ ], this spider bites me, or me... or it bites the
babysitter, or it bites the child in the bed and,
and... oh! This could be very dangerous, right?"
Then I remembered, I remembered that… I
remembered, I remembered that, behind… behind,
of the pants, I was carrying, I was carrying
the hammer.  He carried the hammer.
So I said: "No. I can't, I
can't, I can't catch this spider with a glass. I
can't catch it with a glass. No, no, no. It's
very big, man, it's very big. It's very dangerous. We
have to, we have to, we have to get rid of it," right?
So I picked up the hammer, I picked up the hammer.  And
then I became like this, very attentive,
looking, in the… in silence,
right?  To see where the spider came out.
And suddenly, suddenly his little head poked out,
a little like this, he poked his head out, and I saw, I saw two
eyes that were looking at me like this, fixedly, like this.  And I grabbed:
bang!, and I hit him with a… with the hammer, very
hard: bang!  But the aunt, the aunt was very fast,
she escaped, she got out, she shot out.  And I, uh,
what I did was I hit the… I hit the mirror,
man.  I hit the mirror, I smashed the mirror to pieces:
boom, crash, they fell to the floor,
a lot of, of, of pieces of, of glass fell.
A disaster.  A, a disaster.  And to top it all
off, the spider escaped under
the door.  I saw her go under
the bathroom door and out
the hall to the rest of the house.  Ah!
So I ran away, right?  I went out, I
ran out with the hammer in my hand, behind,
looking for the spider, looking for spiders on
the walls, right?  I didn't see the nanny
anywhere, she wasn't anywhere.
I don't know, he... he would have hidden, I don't know.   I
started looking for the spider because I didn't want it to, I did
n't want it to bite the babysitter or the kid,
right?  You can imagine, right?  A spider like that… it was
huge, that spider was huge, with a lot of
hair, very hairy, eyes… the eyes of a
killer.  She had killer eyes, incredible.
And then I started looking and I saw her
in the living room.  It was in the living room,
on top of the television, wasn't it?  I mean, uh… on top of,
on the, on top of the television,
right?  I came in with the hammer: boom, I blew up the
TV, man.  All the television on the floor!
But the spider kept running: tuck, and hid
behind the pictures.  I arrived with the hammer:
boom, the painting, to hell.  Look,
I took out the paintings in the room,
I took out… there was a vase, a vase that,
that… well, that, that seemed quite expensive,
right?  Of… well, a, a vase of… of… it seemed
expensive, didn't it?  Bim!  I hit the vase.  I loaded,
I loaded some flowerpots, some plants, the pictures
that were on the walls, a table, a chair...
In the end, look, in the end I was already
crazy.  I was like crazy because I saw her appear,
I saw her appear, she looked at me and I said: bang!, I
hit her, and the girl escaped.  I was getting very
nervous.  It was, it was almost a personal thing,
really.  It was a personal thing, because I thought:
"This girl... the spider, no... the spider is making
fun of me, man. She's making fun of me, she's laughing at
me, right? She's laughing at me. I... I, I
don't... I don't like being laughed at," right?
So I was going with the spider all over the
house, right?  Bim, bam, boom!  A lamp: boom!
The lamp, [ __ ] off.  I broke everything,
man.  I broke… I wrecked the whole house, man.  I
messed up the whole house.  And the spider continued.
Behind, he hid, he reappeared, he
poked out a little paw, he poked out his head: pin!, me
with the hammer: pin, pin!  Nothing.  I didn't give him a single one.
I messed up the whole house.  I broke the bottles,
the glasses… The whole house was in shambles!
Suddenly, suddenly I felt a hand
here behind me.  I felt a hand here behind me:
"Stop, stop, you son of a [ __ ]! Stop!"
he said to me.  He was a guy, a square guy, huge, one
of those… one of those who, who works, I don't know,
in the… at the door of the clubs, right?  So,
huge, like a closet, right?  A
built-in closet.  So, a guy like that, who was wearing
a suit and, and, and the, and the, the, the, the shirt
was bursting… all like that, very tight, right?
The buttons were already about to explode.   He
was a guy with incredible muscles,
like the incredible Hulk.  Something like that, right?  One
of those guys who spends his days at the gym.  He
grabbed me from here and said, "Stop, you son of a [ __
]! Stop!"  And I said, "What the hell? What, what,
what? Who is this guy? Who is this guy?"
Who was it going to be?  Who was it going to
be?  Who do you think it was?
The owner of the house, of course.  The owner of the house,
the child's father.  Oh... then he said to me: "What are you
doing, son of a [ __ ]!?"  Told me.  The guy was
insulting me, everything... he said: "You're an idiot!
What are you doing? Stop!"  And I, with the hammer
there: bang, bang.  "Stop, stop!" my uncle said to me,
"Stop!"  In the end he took me from here, didn't he?  Because
if, if not… if he, if he doesn't get me from here, I
won't… I was… I was like crazy trying to
smash this, this… the spider, man.
And in the end, the guy said to me: "Stop, stop, stop, you
son of a [ __ ]!"  And, and in the end I stopped.  I finally stopped, did
n't I?  Me, I saw this guy like this, square, right?  Uh, he
scared me a little too, this guy, right?
Let's see, let's see... the guy said to me: "What have you
done, you son of a [ __ ]? What have you done?
Look how you've destroyed my house!"
And of course, I looked, I looked at myself… I looked around.
The guy was right, he was right.  I mean,
I had messed up everything, man.  The television, the
paintings, the plants, the glasses, the vases,
the lamps, man… the mirrors… I mean, he
had destroyed them all.  All.  Absolutely.
The guy went ballistic, of course.
He became a beast.  He wanted to hit me,
man.  I ran away!  Ah!  He was a very strong guy, was
n't he?  Uh… I went out, I ran away.  Then the guy
said, "No, I'm not going to hit you! I'm not going
to hit you! I'm going to call the police! I'm going to, I'm
going to call the police! I'm going to report you!"  He
wanted, he wanted me to pay for everything, all the
expenses for all the damage, right?  He wanted
me to pay him for everything.  That he… asked me for €10,000,
€10,000.  He said, "This is
very expensive! This is very expensive!"
In the end he wanted me to pay him €10,000, man.   Phew
!  I already… what do you want me to say?  I didn't
have a penny.  I already saw myself in jail.   I
saw myself in jail.  I saw myself in jail.
Thank goodness, thank goodness Marie,
the French nanny, appeared.  She was carrying the child in her arms,
wasn't she?  And, and she finally clarified
the situation a little, right?  He said to him: "No,
look, it was me, it was me who
called you to, to kill, that,
that very big spider that, that I found
in the bathroom. And I called you."
She finally said something, she said something, right?  He said
something, didn't he?  And I, I said: "Of course, of course! It
was a spider. We, we found
a huge spider that can be poisonous, it
can… it can bite the child, it can
bite a person, and it is very dangerous."
And then the guy, the guy said to me: "It
's not poisonous, you idiot!"  Told me.  He called me an
idiot again.  He said to me, "You're an idiot! She
's not poisonous. She's... her name is Petra and she's, and she's, she
's the house pet."  That's what he told me.  He
told me no, that it was a spider
that they had as a pet, right?  There are
people who have a dog, a cat... Well, these,
uh... these people, this family, had a spider.
A spider that they had bought I don't know where,
in a... in a country, one of those countries where it
never rains.  One of those countries that is very hot.  Well,
they had bought that spider there, and it was very expensive.
They had paid a fortune for the [ __ ] spider.  And,
and they loved her very much.  Her name was Petra.
The spider was called Petra.  The spider
was called Petra, man.  Her name was Petra!  I
swear, okay?  I swear, I swear it's true!
The spider was called Petra.  And he told me that it was a
very, very expensive spider.  That they had paid a
fortune for this… for this… for this spider.  That it
wasn't dangerous.  That she was very affectionate.  That she was very,
very affectionate.  Who ate with them.  That he
slept with the child in the bed.  That he was almost,
almost part of the family, my uncle told me.
And the problem… of course, in the end the guy said:
"Well…" In the end, in the end,
he calmed down a little and said: "Well,
it's true that I should have told the
nanny that we had this spider," right?  Because
the nanny had been… she had been working there for a few days
, right?  And the uncles, this man and his wife,
hadn't told him that there was a spider in
the family, so to speak.  That, that, that this,
this pet existed.  And of course, when the nanny
saw the pet, she got so scared… well, it was all
a misunderstanding.  It was all a misunderstanding.
And the guy finally said to me: "Look, well,
I understand that your intention was good."  He told me that, did
n't he?  In the end, in the end, the guy was understanding, was
n't he?  Uh... uh... I... at first I really hated him
, right?  I liked him… I really disliked him,
because he was one of the neighbors who never greeted me,
right?  In fact, he told me: "I've always
disliked you. I've disliked you a lot. No, I don't
like you at all," he told me.  He told me, the guy, of course.
Uh… I was very nervous.  I was very
nervous.  And anyway… of course, I understand it,
right?  Uh... the guy came home, found
a, a, a neighbor... me... he found me there,
hammer in hand, hammering
everywhere.  Clear!  I understand, I
understand that he wanted to kill me.  He wanted to
hit me and, well… I understand.  I understand.
But in the end, well, everything became a
bit clearer.  The man understood that my intention had
been good, that it had all been a
misunderstanding, that the nanny didn't know that, that, that there was
this pet in the house,
this, this spider, that it wasn't dangerous.
Well, well, in the end everything was cleared up
and he let me go.  He left me, he left me… He said:
"Well, look, in the end the things you
broke don't have much value. Nor… they were
already very old and all that. It doesn't matter, nothing happens
."  Okay.  He finally let me go, okay?
And well, in the end, well.  Well, he was good
to me, wasn't he?  Also, I was, I was very young,
right?  I think he felt a little, a little
sorry for me too, right?  And, and nothing, I left.  I
left… I was, I was still in my pajamas, man.   I
was still in my pajamas.  And I went home.
But that's not where it ended, right?  That's
not where it ended.  I went down the stairs, did
n't I?  I was upstairs.  I walked down the
stairs to go home, and then what happened?
Well, since it was very windy, it was
very windy, the door to my house had
closed.  Boom!  And I didn't have the keys, man.
I had gone out, I had gone out with Magui before,
uh, with the hammer in my hand, but I had…
I had, I had forgotten the keys.  I hadn't
taken the keys.  And, and now he was out.
The door had been closed by the wind.   It
was really cold then, it was really cold… It was, it was… I do
n't know, it was December or something like that.  It was really
cold, man, and I couldn't, I couldn't do anything.  I
couldn't get into the house.  It was, I don't know, two o'clock,
six in the morning, more or less.  So I
sat on the stairs.  I sat on the stairs
waiting, waiting, because I didn't have... I had to
call a locksmith, but at that hour I couldn't
call anyone.  I had to wait for
morning to come, right? For it to become light, right?
What happened was, of course, the light went out,
right?  The light would go out every so often,
right?  And I, I had to get up to boom,
flip the switch and turn it on again, right?
And one, one of those times when the light went
out and I went to get up and hit
the switch with my hand… I was looking with my
… I was looking for the switch with my hand,
on the wall, and I touched… I touched something
sort of slimy, with lots of hairs… ah!
Sure enough, sure enough… I turned on the
light, I turned on the light… and it was Petra!  It was, it
was Petra!  There, in front of me, in front of me,
like this, at this distance, looking at me.  She looked at me
with murderous eyes.  And I... I...
You're going to say that I dreamed this,
but no.  I didn't dream it.  It's true.  I swear!   He
smiled at me.  He smiled at me!  He opened his mouth, the spider,
man.  He opened his mouth.  And I saw some teeth.  Some
yellowish teeth.  Oh, how disgusting!  He opened his
mouth and he was, he was smiling, man.  He was
smiling.  Well… he was, he was laughing at
me.  I think he was laughing at me.  He was
pulling my leg, wasn't he?  He was pulling my leg.
Disgusting!  How disgusting and how scary!
So, of course,
all night long, I spent the whole time on the stairs flicking
the light switch.  Hm.  Because I didn't want to, I didn't want
the power to go out.  I didn't want
the light to go out.  Because if the light went out, the spider,
Petra, could arrive at any moment.
I spent the whole night awake, flicking the
switch.  So, until seven in the morning.
Some things happen to me.  Some things happen to me
... I think that... I think that it is... eh,
eh... this day, that day, was the worst day of my
life.  Really.  The worst day of my life.
No, no, no, no.  The worst day of my life,
the worst day of my life was when the gorilla dog thing happened to me
.  The gorilla dog thing was much
worse.  Much worse.  There is no comparison.   The
gorilla dog thing was much worse.
That was it, that
was the worst day of my life.
Someday, someday I'll tell the story of the
gorilla dog.  Next week,
uh... next week I'll tell you the
story of the gorilla dog.  That's right,
that was it, that was it...
Guys, see you.  See you later!